Natonek, Hans; Papers ger004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Literary Works, 1924-1925; 1933-1949; 1958-1963; 3; 2.5 cubic ft.
  - Short Stories, 1924; 1938-1943; 1949; 1958; 1961-1963; 3.3
    - Notebook of a Nonconformist, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 63)
    - Not Our Kind of People, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 64)
    - Old Enough to be Her Father, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 65)
    - Prayer's Progress, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 66)
    - Prophetie und "Wishful Thinking", ca. 1941-1943 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 67)
    - Quartet, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 68)
    - Revolt Against TV Polls, ca. 1958 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 69)
    - Roof and Key, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 70)
    - Roses of Konopischt, ca. 1963 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 71)
    - Schlapanitz - Eckensteher Der Weltgeschichte, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 72)
    - Short Short Horse Opera, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 73)
    - Should You Mind Your Own Business, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 74)
    - Sohn (Rodin), Der, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 75)
    - Sometimes Sorry for Yourself, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 76)
    - Son, The, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 77)
    - Stain on the Wall, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 78)
    - Stranger Discovers America, A, 1943 December (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 79)
    - There Goes Beulah, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 80)
    - Timing, ca. 1943 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 81)
    - Tools, Toys, and Toils, ca. 1941-1943 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 82)
    - Traveler Returns, A, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 83)
    - Unbesiegt, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 84)
    - Unschuldiger Betruger, 1963 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 85)
    - Vergessenen Jabre, Die, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 86)
    - Verlaine Und Sohn, ca. 1940 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 87)
    - Verschlossene Schrank, Der, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 88)
    - Verwirrung Um Peterle, ca. 1941-1943 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 89)
    - Vice Hardest to Suppress, The, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 90)
    - Von Arzten Und Alten Patienten, 1963 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 91)
    - Walk to the Mailbox, A, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 92)
    - Wes in Die Tiefe, Der, 1962 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 93)
    - Welcome, Pardner, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 94)
    - Wenn Es Nur Abstrakt Ist..., 1961 April 14 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 95)
    - Wiederholt Sich Die Geschichte, ca. 1940 (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 96)
    - Zum Experiment Des Selbstubersetzens, Undated (Box 3 (3-Literary Works), Folder 97)
  - Fragments, undated; 3.4
    - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, Fragments, Notes, Undated (Box 4 (3-Literary Works), Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1960-1961; 1963-1964; 3.5
    - 1. "At the Grave of Rainer Maria Rilke", The Poetry Review", LII, no. 3, 1961 July-1961 September
    - 2. "Between Two Languages", The Freeman, 1953 April 6
    - 3. "Bildnisse in Epigrammen", Deutsche Rundschau, 90, 1, 1964 January
    - 4. "Dienst am Kinden", in Hier Schreibt Berlin, Herbert Gunther, ed., MĂźnchen, Paul List Verlag, 1963
    - 5. "Should You Mind Your Own Business", Your Life, 1960 July